<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Larry Earl Wraight, Strategic Intervention Coach]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Larry Earl Wraight, Strategic Intervention Coach]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/finger-lakes-coaching/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 14:16:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/finger-lakes-coaching/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5ddeb77a-2a53-488c-9062-6fa59ccd024e.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/finger-lakes-coaching/the-finger-lakes-region-is-a-blessing-in-this-world-the-ice/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">be4a727b-466c-4156-9251-df804fee8370</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 14:15:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Infidelity and Post Traumatic Stress Disorder]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Infidelity and Post Traumatic Stress Disorder</h1><p>(This article is reprinted from "Infidelity and Post Traumatic Stress Disorder" found on Marriage Advocates) While not all betrayed spouses experience Post Traumatic Stress Disorder, many experience it to varying degrees. According to the National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), PTSD affects 7.7 million American adults.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/94cce930f1c4159a03e5895e8b856d8b7bd473e1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://affaircare.com/articles/infidelity-and-post-traumatic-stress-disorder/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">29b0c394-1f4e-4bb5-8f1e-7b71df74714d</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 14:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blueberries show promise as treatment for post-traumatic stress disorder]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Blueberries show promise as treatment for post-traumatic stress disorder</h1><p>Up to 8 percent of people in the U.S. suffer from post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD) as the result of witnessing or being the victim of a traumatic event. People with PTSD have been in a situation in which they were at risk of death, serious injury or sexual violence or have seen first-hand loved ones faces such threats.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/241dafc1e8e278bb34d1bb84d259173731708143.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2015/03/150330134405.htm?trendmd-shared=0</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b646a4ad-5ee3-4f77-afbc-fc2795edd335</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 14:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eliminating Negative Habits and Emotions to Create a New Future, Dr. Joe Dispenza]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Eliminating Negative Habits and Emotions to Create a New Future, Dr. Joe Dispenza</h1><p>A Free Video on Eliminating Negative Habits and Emotions to Create a New Future with Dr. Joe Dispenza http://www.learn.hayhouseu.com/joedispenza-video2-breakoldhabits-rl</p><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/vahj1ThiexotieMo/02d4d1c4827c5bd8cf1ea2ad3ddb39ec/noop.jpg?input=http%3A%2F%2Fdfsm9194vna0o.cloudfront.net%2F1200731-0-DRJoenew166x178.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.learn.hayhouseu.com/joedispenza-video2-breakoldhabits-rl</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">93027745-967d-4466-9663-0f0d54d7e567</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 14:02:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brain caught 'filing' memories during rest]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Brain caught 'filing' memories during rest</h1><p>Memories formed in one part of the brain are replayed and transferred to a different area of the brain during rest, according to a new study in rats.The finding suggests that replay of previous experiences during rest is important for memory consolidation, a process whereby the brain stabilizes and preserves memories for quick recall in the future.</p><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/vahj1ThiexotieMo/c3d6b72a997af0234028cb0dd6b26cf7/noop.jpg?input=https%3A%2F%2Fimages.sciencedaily.com%2F2016%2F04%2F160418120102_1_540x360.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2016/04/160418120102.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">638f6f07-afcf-4f11-974b-670bee75208e</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 13:58:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>I am, Larry Earl Wraight.  I was blessed with 30 years of love and support before I discovered any suffering in life.  I had pain, but no suffering for a long time.   A strong foundation of love, support and service to others was graciously given to me.  I am so grateful for the chance to love, support and serve others at this time in my life. The fifth child of Earl and Lucille Wraight and the baby brother to Gail, Joan, Norma and Beth.  I was the only child in my family without a boy’s name at birth:  Earlena.  My parents had given up on my father’s desire for a son until Earlena was born and thankfully renamed me, Larry. I was raised in the small town of Lyons, NY to my loving family and community. Life was not perfect at 12 Bear Street, but it was close.   I thrived with my extended family close by and a community of friends who provided a loving extension to my family. I went on home visits with my mother as a preteen, when she worked for the Dept. of Social Services.  I tagged along with my father when he did free plumbing work for elderly people who could not afford to maintain their homes.  I was trained early by my family, church, and community in a life of service to others.  I was a three sport athlete, in choir and played french horn in Lyons Central School.  My senior year of high school I arrived early all spring to play and say goodbye to the french horn. In college, I focused on wrestling, leaving my music and other sports interests behind.  I wrestled for three years in college and cemented being a wrestler as part of my core identity.  I was a county champion and co-captain wrestler in high school, the first freshman on SUNY at Oswego varsity and third in New York State as a sophomore.  I accomplished less than I could have on the mat, however I took on the character traits of a wrestler into my adult life. I was happily married for 13 years and we were blessed with two children:  Meghann and Brian.  I was devastated by our marriage failed and created a story of suffering which undermined my life for to long. My first career was in Child Protective Services.  For 29 years I worked on the dark side of life.  I sought out the most evil and disfunctional parents I could find and attempted to change or control their ability to harm children.  Everyday of that work:  I feared the death or demise of children and gave my all.  I used my fear to excel for a long time. At 52 years of age I was burned out in life;  burdened with post traumatic stress from my work, failed personal relationships, the pain of my father’s debilitating alzheimers, followed by his and eight other deaths within 8 months of people I loved.  I reached a breaking point.  I stood in the doorway of death and the door was wide open. I was able to survive six more months until I could retire from CPS.  In January 2003, I began a healing journey that still continues to this day. My first 6 months of retirement I studied Dr. Phil’s books and applied his lessons to myself.  Next I lost 100 lb. in 8 months.  My healing had just begun.  Over the past decade I have healed the suffering in my life and can feel the pains of life in a more healthy manner.  I have rephrased the story of my life to one more consistent with love and acceptance. I am now on a path to thrive and excel in life again.  I have had some great moments of thriving before, however the integration of my life experiences present a special time for me now. October 2011, I was diagnosed with Adult Attention Deficit Disorder and began to study for my Coaching career.  For me untreated ADD  and PTSD explained the suffering I had accumulated in my life, as I had attempted to achieve my highest goals.  My personal growth over the past two years has presented me with an opportunity to return to a life of service at a whole new level. In coaching I find the rewards of personal service, and I love working on the bright side of life.  The lessons I learned working in pain, trauma and death have armed me with great knowledge and skills to help others.  The lessons I have learned in healing my suffering have reopened my ability to thrive in life.  I am incredibly grateful for the blessings of love and connection that have been so freely showered on me so far in my life.  I am grateful for my continuing chance of a life of service to others.  I am grateful for the love and support of my family and friends as a great sense of wellness fills me today. Winters in my life; Big Bart dieing, betrayal, refusing to love, emotional eating, when CPS was a hostile work environment.My thriving depends on;  Meditation, education, diet, exercise, and medication for my ADD.  Journaling, loving and connecting with others in order to thrive.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/finger-lakes-coaching/i-am-larry-earl-wraight-i-was-blessed-with-30-years-of-lo/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ba9d1d16-a253-478d-b366-6a1611898012</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 23:08:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>